<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Saprilian Hidayat</title>
    <link>https://examplesite.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Saprilian Hidayat</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://examplesite.com/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 23:15:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://examplesite.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Find-IT UGM: Hoter Price Prediction with Pycaret</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/projects/reproducible-computational-drug-discovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/projects/reproducible-computational-drug-discovery/</guid>
      <description>Problem Overview Kyozo, a prominent global hotel chain, is seeking the assistance of a data consultant to develop a price prediction model for their upcoming hotel ventures. As the chosen data consultant, you have been provided with a dataset containing information from thousands of their current hotels. However, Kyozo&amp;rsquo;s team lacks expertise in handling data, and thus, you are tasked with matching columns and values to various hotel examples for accurate predictions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/about/</guid>
      <description>In my daytime, I am studying in Padjadjaran University as Mathematics student.
At night, I&amp;rsquo;m a content creator developing tutorials in data science for the following platforms:
📝 Medium Blogs. 💻 GitHub You can also connect with me at the following social platforms:
Twitter LinkedIn Instagram </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Text Analysist : Emirate Airline Reviews using Count Words, Bigram, and Trigram</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/projects/acetylcholinesterase/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/projects/acetylcholinesterase/</guid>
      <description>Problem Understanding This data science project focused on analyzing customer reviews of Emirates Airlines obtained from the https://www.airlinequality.com/airline-reviews/emirates/. By applying text analysis and natural language processing (NLP) techniques, the sentiment of the reviews was categorized as positive, negative, or neutral. The findings revealed that the majority of the reviews (1407) were classified as positive, indicating a high level of satisfaction among Emirates Airlines&amp;rsquo; users. However, there were also negative reviews (620) and neutral reviews (214), suggesting areas for improvement in the airline&amp;rsquo;s services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vending Machine Analysist -- Revou Capstone Project (MSIB Kampus Merdeka)</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/projects/erpred/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/projects/erpred/</guid>
      <description>Business Overview The vending machine company is having several vending machines from various locations in Central New Jersey. The locations include a library, a mall, an office location, and a manufacturing location. The company would like to find multiple insights from the vending machine data to improve its performance. The dataset is recorded from 5 different machines for 8 months.
imitation: The dataset date’s time is only from January to August 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infographics</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/infographics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/infographics/</guid>
      <description>I also create hand-drawn infographics and illustrations to summarize the key concepts in data science and machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to master Streamlit for Data Science</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/blogs/how-to-master-streamlit-for-data-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/blogs/how-to-master-streamlit-for-data-science/</guid>
      <description>Preview The essential Streamlit for all your data science needs To build a web app you’d typically use such Python web frameworks as Django and Flask. But the steep learning curve and the big time investment for implementing these apps present a major hurdle.
Streamlit makes the app creation process as simple as writing Python scripts!
In this article, you’ll learn how to master Streamlit when getting started with data science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Bioinformatics</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/blogs/what-is-bioinformatics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/blogs/what-is-bioinformatics/</guid>
      <description>Introduction So you probably have heard of the term Bioinformatics before, but did not get the chance to learn more about what it is and what it can do.
In this article, I will be giving you a brief high-level overview of this exciting field of Bioinformatics. Thus, the article will be comprehensible to those coming from biology or computer backgrounds alike.
As a biologist, I have self-taught myself data science and coding (R and Python) after several years of persistence (initially quitting a couple of times the coding concept just kind of clicked at some point in time).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 1st post</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/page/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/page/</guid>
      <description>Desc Text.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
